<resources>
    <string name="app_name">NavaneethKP_Saarang_Android</string>

    <string name="Buzzer">Is lightning-speed pouncing your thing?
        Or perhaps, edging out a rival team in a matter of seconds?
        If your answer is a yes, leave aside all other pressing issues
        and get ready to pounce, \'cause Saarang Buzzer Quiz is a\'beckonin! </string>

    <string name="India">The India Quiz is one of Saarang\'s
        most awaited events. Join us as we wind our way through
        the myriad peoples and cultures across the length and breadth
        of the wonder that is India. A quiz about anything Indian. </string>

    <string name="Cornucopia"> You may have participated in craft events like greeting card making or doll
        making or maybe even best out of waste.
        Here, we ask you to think a little out of the box... literally! So, here\'s the deal,
        there will be two "secret ingredients" (hopefully in a box, Masterchef anyone?) and you guys
        have to make a piece (read: work of art) with either or both of those "ingredients" as
        the main elements. Easy peasy right? Well, when we ask you to make a piece, it can literally be anything,
        absolutely anything. It can move, rotate, look pretty
        or even been pulled apart in front of the judge! Well, we do stick to our motto of creative freedom</string>

    <string name="Rangrez"> We all have been doing the same old boring and generic sketching/painting
        competitions all our school life. Well, this isn\'t school anymore and everything in college
        comes with a twist! You do have to sketch or paint (No restrictions there), but we want you add
        your own little style and your own tang to an otherwise boring pattern. Bring back a folk style
        into fashion or add your own modern touch to art filled with enchantments and magic!
        Happy painting (or sketching, whatever you choose really).</string>

    <string name="Fifa">No gaming tournament is complete without this title!! Saarang brings to you a
        complete console based FIFA 17 tournament for all the soccer die-hards out there</string>

    <string name="Dota">Come and take part in one of the country\’s
        biggest DOTA 2 tournaments, where teams will battle it out
        for ultimate glory and walk away with exorbitant prizes.</string>

    <string name="c1">Nathan \n9952017387 </string>
    <string name="c2">Avinaash \n9894799418 </string>
    <string name="c3">Archit \n9176492387 </string>
    <string name="c4">Nivia \n9445125963 </string>
    <string name="c5">Deepak \n7401205049  </string>
    <string name="c6">Subash \n967741567 </string>


</resources>
